http://www.isug.com/contact/privacy-policy

Independent SAP Technical User Group logo
AboutMembershipOfficers and DirectorsEventsCalendarConferencesWebinarsUser Group MeetingsWorkshopsPast EventsTrainingNewsISUG NewsPartner NewsEvent NewsForumISUG-TECH CommunityPowerBuilderInfomakerPowerServerASESQL AnywhereReplication ServerIQPowerDesignerHANAERPNetWeaverBusiness ObjectsOther ProductsOff Topic DiscussionsNews DiscussionsContact
Independent SAP Technical User Group logo
Join Now Login
HomeContactPrivacy Policy
Privacy Policy ISUG-TECH (ISUG-TECH)  is very aware of our customer's needs for security and privacy. To that end the following document describes how we control you and your organizations private information. In our privacy statement we will outline: What personally identifiable information ISUG-TECH collects. What personally identifiable information third parties collect through the Web site. What organization collects the information. How ISUG-TECH uses the information. With whom ISUG-TECH may share user information. What choices are available to users regarding collection, use and distribution of the information. What types of security procedures are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under Socious control. How users can correct any inaccuracies in the information. Please read the following document carefully, and if you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.. Information CollectionThe ISUG-TECH is the sole owner of the information collected on my.isug.com. The ISUG-TECH collects information from our users at several different points on our Web site.
RegistrationIn order to use this Web site, a user must first complete the registration form. During registration a user is required to give contact information (such as name and email address). We use this information to contact the user about services on our site for which he has expressed interest. It is optional for the user to provide demographic and profile information, but it is encouraged so we can provide a more personalized experience on our site.  User and Group InformationOther members of the ISUG-TECH may view information you provide about yourself and your organization. This information includes such items as Email Address and other information you provide. At any time you may opt out of allowing other users to view this information. By removing the information from the system, other users will not be able to see it. The ISUG-TECH does not store this information after you remove it - in order to enable it again you must re-enter the information. Organization pages include basic demographic information about type of institution, location, mailing address, contact phone number, and contact person. Organization can opt out of some of these pieces of information (contact phone number, contact person) by not providing the information. VendorsVendor Partners are never given access to user pages, but are able to view organization pages.  Forum CommunityDuring your use of this Web site, you may wish to participate in our Forum Community by asking questions or responding to other users' questions. Any information you provide within this area may be viewed by other members of the ISUG-TECH community. It is encouraged that you never provide any sensitive or private information in this area. When these items are displayed for others to see, ISUG-TECH website will display your name, your message, your signature file, your organization's name and their logo.  Technical LibraryDuring your use of this Web site, you may wish to participate in our Technical Library by downloading or providing files for other users. Any information you provide within this area may be viewed by other members of the ISUG-TECH. It is encouraged that you never provide any sensitive or private information in this area. ISUG-TECH Website Vendor Partners are never allowed to view client files, or other Vendor files. Vendor partners may only see files that their organization has added.  News NetworkDuring your use of this Web site, you may wish to participate in our News Network by providing news and information relating to the IT industry. Any information you provide within this area may be viewed by other members of the ISUG-TECH. It is encouraged that you never provide any sensitive or private information in this area. When these items are displayed for others to see, the ISUG-TECH website will display your organization's name and their logo.
Information Use ProfileWe store information that we collect through cookies, and log files and users to create a profile of our users. A profile is stored information that we keep on individual users that details their viewing preferences. Consequently, collected information is tied to the users personally identifiable information to provide offers and improve the content of the site for the user. This profile is used to tailor a user's visit to our Web site. Your profile will only be shared as part of an aggregate form with no personal or identifiable information.  CookiesA cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. We only use session ID cookies. For the session ID cookie, once users close the browser, the cookie simply terminates.  Log FilesLike most standard Web site servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information, and are never given to third parties. Aggregate information may be used by the ISUG-TECH in order to provide vendor partners with more detailed information on our clients usage, and for the ISUG-TECH to enhance our services.
Communications from the Site Vendor MailingsWhile vendors are never given email addresses, they may request us to send occasional emails to our membership. You as a user have a right to opt out of receiving these emails, and may do so by updating your profile online. By selecting 'Prevent vendors from sending email to you' will stop any further mailings. Alternately, you may send an email to This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it. and a support representative will handle your request promptly.  Special Offers and UpdatesWe send all new members a welcoming email to verify password and username. Established members will occasionally receive information from the ISUG-TECH and a newsletter.  Service AnnouncementsOn rare occasions it is necessary to send out a strictly service related announcement. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance we might send users an email. Generally, users may not opt-out of these communications, though they can deactivate their account. However, these communications are not promotional in nature.  Customer ServiceWe communicate with users on a regular basis to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account we reply via email or phone, in accordance with the users wishes.
Sharing Legal DisclaimerThough we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site.  Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable)We share aggregated demographic information with our partners. This is not linked to any personally identifiable information.  Third Party IntermediariesWe use an outside shipping company to ship orders. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes.  LinksThis Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we, the ISUG-TECH, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.
SecurityThis Web site takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the Web site, their information is protected both online and off-line.Should you ever be need to provide sensitive information (such as a credit card number and/or social security number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - SSL. While on a secure page, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when users are just "surfing". While we currently do not collect any of this type of information, it is possible we will provide services requiring this need in the future. While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All of our users' information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Furthermore, ALL employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Every quarter, as well as any time new policies are added, our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our users' information is protected. Finally, the servers that store personally identifiable information are in a secure environment,. If users have any questions about the security at our Web site, users can send an email to This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.  Correcting/Updating/Deleting/Deactivating Personal InformationIf a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as zip code, phone, email or postal address), or if a user no longer desires our service, we provide a way to correct, update or delete/deactivate users' personally identifiable information. This can usually be done at the on your profile or by emailing our Customer Support at This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.. Or, contact us via contact information listed below.  Notification of ChangesIf we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected. If, however, we are going to use users' personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify users via email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. However, if users have opted out of all communication with the site, or deleted/deactivated their account, then they will not be contacted, nor will their personal information be used in this new manner. In addition, if we make any material changes in our privacy practices that do not affect user information already stored in our database, we will post a prominent notice on our Web site notifying users of the change. In some cases where we post a notice we will also email users, who have opted to receive communications from us, notifying them of the changes in our privacy practices.  Contact InformationIf users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at:Email: This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.
ISUG-TECH13121 Louetta Road #1245Cypress, Texas 77429Join Now Login AboutMembershipOfficers and DirectorsEventsCalendarConferencesWebinarsUser Group MeetingsWorkshopsPast EventsTrainingNewsISUG NewsPartner NewsEvent NewsForumISUG-TECH CommunityPowerBuilderInfomakerPowerServerASESQL AnywhereReplication ServerIQPowerDesignerHANAERPNetWeaverBusiness ObjectsOther ProductsOff Topic DiscussionsNews DiscussionsContact
